{
    "id": "1beceda9d91f4e4c9b759d06b8d85848",
    "title": "Prepositions of Time – At, On, In",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "40b1b13dc8634e9db9a92295c2e64806",
            "title": "Prepositions of Time | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I usually get up ………………… six o’clock.",
                    "description": "We use at with clock times.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Phone me ……………… lunchtime.",
                    "description": "We use at with clock times.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I work best ………………. the evening.",
                    "description": "We use ‘in’ with parts of the day. For example, we say in the morning, in the afternoon and in the evening. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I usually go for a walk ……………….. the morning.",
                    "description": "We use ‘in’ with parts of the day. For example, we say in the morning, in the afternoon and in the evening. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met …………….. a cold afternoon in winter.",
                    "description": "We use ‘on’ when we say which morning / afternoon / etc., we are talking about.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will call you ……………. Sunday.",
                    "description": "We use ‘on’ with days.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are you doing …………….. the weekend?",
                    "description": "We can say at the weekend or on the weekend.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They got married ……………… the week after Easter.",
                    "description": "We use in for longer periods.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are having the house painted …………… Easter.",
                    "description": "We use ‘at’ to talk about the whole of the holidays at Christmas, Easter etc.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wrote the book …………. a month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are you free .......................?",
                    "description": "Prepositions are not used in expressions of time before next, last, this, that, each, every etc.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in this evening",
                        "this evening",
                        "on this evening"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s meet ………………",
                    "description": "Prepositions are not used in expressions of time before next, last, this, that, each, every etc.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on one day",
                        "in one day",
                        "one day"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}